American Civil Liberties Union Records: Subgroup 2, Organizational Matters Series, 1947-1995: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 1: Organizational Matters, 1930-1995; 582 boxes
  - Subseries 1M: Attacks and Commendations, 1936-1982; 9 boxes
    - Commendations, 1945-1978; more than 30 folders
      - President Eisenhower Commendations of Civil Rights, 1953; 1 folder (Box 612, Folder 18)
      - General, 1954; 3 folders (Box 612, Folder 19-21)
      - Department of the Army, 1956; 1 folder (Box 612, Folder 22)
      - Press Comments on ACLU, 1952-1957; 1 folder (Box 612, Folder 23)
      - State Department in 1955 Yearbook on Human Rights, 1957; 1 folder (Box 612, Folder 24)
      - Stevenson, Adlai E, 1960; 1 folder (Box 612, Folder 25)
      - Rockefeller, Nelson A, 1960; 1 folder (Box 612, Folder 26)
      - Eisenhower, Dwight D, 1960; 1 folder (Box 612, Folder 27)
      - Wagner, Robert F, 1960; 1 folder (Box 612, Folder 28)
      - Kennedy, John F, 1962; 1 folder (Box 612, Folder 29)
      - General, 1965; 1 folder (Box 612, Folder 30)
      - El Jurista - Roger Baldwin Commendation, 1965; 1 folder (Box 612, Folder 31)
      - General: Commendations, 1966; 1 folder (Box 612, Folder 32)
      - The American Isrealite, 1966; 1 folder (Box 612, Folder 33)
      - Herling, John - Washington Daily News, 1966; 1 folder (Box 612, Folder 34)
      - Navy Does not Consider ACLU Affiliation as Derogatory, 1966; 1 folder (Box 612, Folder 35)
      - Johnson, Lyndon B, 1964; 1968; 1 folder (Box 612, Folder 36)
      - General, 1970; 1 folder (Box 612, Folder 37)
      - Warren, Earl: 50th Anniversary Chairperson, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 612, Folder 38)
      - Baldwin, Roger N.: Article, 1978; 1 folder (Box 612, Folder 39)
  - Subseries 1N: Miscellaneous, 1938-1987; 10 boxes
    The Organizational Miscellaneous subseries (4.2 linear feet) contains various materials concerning structural and functional matters of the ACLU. Arranged chronologically by year and alphabetically within each year, this subseries is divided into four headings: miscellaneous, deaths, financial, and requests for information. The material under miscellaneous includes guides, memoranda, organizational and office materials, statements, articles, book proposals, project proposals, requests for speakers, speeches, and material concerned with ACLU social events. The deaths heading contains ACLU resolutions on the deaths of prominent civil libertarians, including Arthur Garfield Hays. Under the financial heading the researcher will find accountant reports and information concerning funds, grants, budget, and investments. Requests for information contains correspondence requesting information regarding the ACLU or other civil liberty issues. These requests come from members, newspapers and other publications, and lawyers. Included in these files are the ACLU responses.
    - Civil Liberties Educational Fund, Miscellaneous, 1938; 1 folder (Box 613, Folder 1)
    - Tax Exemption, 1938-1946; 1 folder (Box 613, Folder 1a)
    - Baldwin Statement on FBI, Miscellaneous, 1949; 1 folder (Box 613, Folder 2)
    - Comments on Baldwin - Hoover Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1949; 1 folder (Box 613, Folder 3)
    - Villiard, Oswald Garrison, Deaths, 1949; 1 folder (Box 613, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, Request for Information and Assistance, 1949-1950; 1 folder (Box 613, Folder 5)
    - Proposed Los Angeles Poll - "Smith Act v. Freedom of Expression", Miscellaneous, 1952; 1 folder (Box 613, Folder 6)
    - Filing of "Confidential" Material, Miscellaneous, 1952; 1 folder (Box 613, Folder 7)
    - Foundations and Civil Liberties, 1953; 1 folder (Box 613, Folder 7a)
    - Reynolds, Ruth, Miscellaneous, 1953; 1 folder (Box 613, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, Request for Information, 1953; 2 folders (Box 613, Folder 9-10)
    - Hays, Arthur Garfield, Deaths, 1954; 1 folder (Box 613, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, Requests for Information, 1954; 2 folders (Box 613, Folder 12-13)
    - Articles, Miscellaneous, 1955; 1 folder (Box 613, Folder 14)
    - Bill of Rights Day, Miscellaneous, 1955; 1 folder (Box 613, Folder 15)
    - Cooper Union Series on Civil Liberties, Miscellaneous, 1955; 1 folder (Box 613, Folder 16)
    - Government Security Program, Proposed Research Project, Miscellaneous, 1955; 1 folder (Box 613, Folder 17)
    - Office Memos, Miscellaneous, 1955; 1 folder (Box 613, Folder 18)
    - Organizational Matters, Miscellaneous, 1955; 1 folder (Box 613, Folder 19)
    - Efficiency Survey, Miscellaneous, 1955; 1 folder (Box 613, Folder 20)
    - Survey of National Office Organization and Procedures and Its Relations, Miscellaneous, 1955; 1 folder (Box 613, Folder 21)
    - The Cooper Union Arthur Garfield Hays Memorial Meeting, Deaths, 1955; 1 folder (Box 614, Folder 1)
    - Hays, Arthur G. - Eulogies, Deaths, 1955; 1 folder (Box 614, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, Requests for Information, 1955; 1 folder (Box 614, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, Requests for Information, 1955; 1 folder (Box 614, Folder 4)
    - Ferman's Cocktail-Supper Party Guest List, Miscellaneous, 1956; 1 folder (Box 614, Folder 5)
    - Raymond, Allen: "The People's Right to Know.", Miscellaneous, 1956; 1 folder (Box 614, Folder 6)
    - Field, Marshall, Deaths, 1956; 1 folder (Box 614, Folder 7)
    - Johnson, Dr. Charles S., Deaths, 1956; 1 folder (Box 614, Folder 8)
    - Wood, L. Hollingsworth, Deaths, 1956; 1 folder (Box 614, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, Requests for Information, 1956; 2 folders (Box 614, Folder 10-11)
    - Re: ACLU, Requests for Information, 1956; 1 folder (Box 614, Folder 12)
    - Bancroft-Whitney Co., Requests for Information, 1956; 1 folder (Box 614, Folder 13)
    - Cartoon Exhibit, Illinois Division, Miscellaneous, 1957; 1 folder (Box 614, Folder 14)
    - Constitution and By-Laws of ACLU, Miscellaneous, 1957; 1 folder (Box 614, Folder 15)
    - The New School for Social Research, Miscellaneous, 1957; 1 folder (Box 614, Folder 16)
    - Research Foundation Proposal, Miscellaneous, 1957; 1 folder (Box 614, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous, Requests for Information, 1957; 1 folder (Box 614, Folder 18)
    - Re: ACLU, Requests for Information, 1957; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 1)
    - "Journal of Human Relations", Requests for Information, 1957; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 2)
    - Bean, Barton: "Pressure for Freedom: The American Civil Liberties Union" Miscellaneous, 1958; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 3)
    - "Race and Criminal Statistics", Miscellaneous, 1958; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 4)
    - School Integration, Miscellaneous, 1958; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 5)
    - Siegel, Lawrence, Miscellaneous, 1958; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 6)
    - Tanenhaus, Joseph: "The ACLU and the Communist Movement: 1920-1954" Miscellaneous, 1958; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, Deaths, 1958; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 8)
    - Board Resolutions, Deaths, 1958; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 9)
    - Davis, Elmer, Deaths, 1958; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 10)
    - New York Hospital Strike, Miscellaneous, 1959; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 11)
    - Addams, J. - ACLU Connection, Deaths, 1959; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 12)
    - Annual Report, Miscellaneous, 1959; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 13)
    - Church/State Proposed Pamphlet, Miscellaneous, 1959; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 14)
    - Collective Bargaining Agreement, Miscellaneous, 1959; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 15)
    - 86th Congress Report, Miscellaneous, 1959; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 16)
    - Ernst's Project Proposals, Miscellaneous, 1959; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 17)
    - Florina Lasker Fellows, Miscellaneous, 1959; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 18)
    - House Un-American Activities Committee Proposed Pamphlet, Miscellaneous, 1959; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 19)
    - "Inside ACLU", Miscellaneous, 1959; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 20)
    - Office Memos, Miscellaneous, 1959; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 21)
    - Publications Program, Miscellaneous, 1959; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 22)
    - Requests for Speakers, Miscellaneous, 1959; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 23)
    - Speeches, Miscellaneous, 1959; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous, Financial, 1959; 1 folder (Box 615, Folder 25)
    - Requests for Information, Miscellaneous, 1959; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 1)
    - Re: ACLU, Requests for Information, 1959; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 2)
    - Rights of Criminal Indigent Defendants, Requests for Information, 1959; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 3)
    - Compulsory Vaccination, Miscellaneous, 1960; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 4)
    - Arthur Garfield Hays Memorial at NYU, Miscellaneous, 1955-1960; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 5)
    - ACLU Publications Program, Miscellaneous, 1961; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 6)
    - Benign Quotas in Interracial Housing, Miscellaneous, 1961; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 7)
    - Hays Endowment Committee, Miscellaneous, 1961; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 8)
    - Marshall Civil Liberties Trust, 11sc, 1961; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 9)
    - Phoebe Waterman Foundation, Miscellaneous, 1961; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 10)
    - NYU Civil Liberties Center, Miscellaneous, 1957-1961; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 11)
    - Mathews, Prof. Robert E., Requests for Information, 1961; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 12)
    - Arthur Garfield Hays Memorial Fund, Miscellaneous, 1962; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 13)
    - "Autopsy on Operation Abolition", Miscellaneous, 1962; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 14)
    - "Communist Target - Youth", Miscellaneous, 1962; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 15)
    - CBS Radio Announcement on Civil Liberties, Miscellaneous, 1962; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 16)
    - Government Aid to Church-Related Colleges and Universities, Miscellaneous, 1962; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 17)
    - Indian Affairs Grant, Miscellaneous, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 18)
    - Race Issues, Miscellaneous, 1962; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 19)
    - Student Civil Liberties Research Service, Miscellaneous, 1962; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 20)
    - Emerson, Prof. Thomas I., Requests for Information, 1962; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 21)
    - Civil Rights Office in the White House, Miscellaneous, 1963; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 22)
    - "Do Lie Detectors Lie?", Miscellaneous, 1963; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 23)
    - "East Side West Side" - CBS show, Miscellaneous, 1963; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 24)
    - Film List, Miscellaneous, 1963; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 25)
    - Florina Lasker Civil Liberties Award, Miscellaneous, 1963; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 26)
    - Arthur Garfield Hays Civil Liberties Program, Miscellaneous, 1963; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 27)
    - "How Americans Protest", Miscellaneous, 1963; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 28)
    - Jimenez, P. - Political Asylum, Miscellaneous, 1963; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 29)
    - Judge Jerome Frank Award, Miscellaneous, 1963; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 30)
    - Memo Concerning Issues and Cooperation between Operations and Development, Miscellaneous, 1963; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 31)
    - Proposed Conference with John F. Kennedy, Miscellaneous, 1963; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 32)
    - Frank Wilkinson Problem, Miscellaneous, 1963; 1 folder (Box 616, Folder 33)
    - Marshall Fund Grant, Financial, 1963; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 1)
    - Baldwin Portrait, 1964; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 2)
    - Gibbons, R. Editorial, 1964; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 3)
    - Markman, Charles - "The Noblest Cry" - ACLU History, 1964; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 4)
    - Proposed Southern Regional Conference, 1964; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 5)
    - Accountant's Report, Financial, 1964; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 6)
    - Re: Affiliate Relationship, Request for Information, 1964; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 7)
    - ACLU Retirement Plan, 1965; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 8)
    - Cartoons for Possible Civil Liberties Use, 1965; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 9)
    - Coxe, Spencer Article on Work of the ACLU, 1965; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 10)
    - Employment of Management Consulting Firm, 1965; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 11)
    - File Department, 1965; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 12)
    - Films, 1965; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 13)
    - Freedom of Religion in the Fellowship of Reconciliation Tax Case, 1965; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 14)
    - Arthur Garfield Hays Civil Liberties Program, 1965; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 15)
    - Markman, C. - "The Noblest Cry", 1965; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 16)
    - Princeton University Archives, 1965; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 17)
    - Publications, 1965; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 18)
    - Revision of Staff Assignments and Responsibilities, 1965; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous, Financial, 1965; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 20)
    - Sacco and Vanzetti, Request for Information, 1965; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 21)
    - Abstract of Civil Liberties Cases for Dramatization, 1966; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 22)
    - Annual Report, 1966; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 23)
    - Arthur Garfield Hays Civil Liberties Program, 1966; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 24)
    - Book Proposal, 1966; 1 folder (Box 617, Folder 25)
    - Civil Liberties and Education Fund, 1966; 1 folder (Box 618, Folder 1)
    - Communications Analysts Barton-Gillet Co, 1966; 1 folder (Box 618, Folder 2)
    - "Frontiers in the Struggle for Civil Liberties", 1966; 1 folder (Box 618, Folder 3)
    - "Jim Crow Justice", 1966; 1 folder (Box 618, Folder 4)
    - Kennan-Reitman Dispute, 1966; 1 folder (Box 618, Folder 5)
    - Lamont, C. Controversy, 1966; 1 folder (Box 618, Folder 6)
    - Markmann, C. - "The Noblest Cry", 1966; 1 folder (Box 618, Folder 7)
    - New York Times, 1966; 1 folder (Box 618, Folder 8)
    - Roger Baldwin Foundation, 1966; 1 folder (Box 618, Folder 9)
    - W.W. Norton Book Agreement, 1966; 1 folder (Box 618, Folder 10)
    - War Claims, 1966; 1 folder (Box 618, Folder 11)
    - Requests, Financial, 1966; 1 folder (Box 618, Folder 12)
    - Budget Working Papers, Financial, 1966; 1 folder (Box 618, Folder 13)
    - National Organization Financial Statements, Financial, 1966; 1 folder (Box 618, Folder 14)
    - Soll and Aronin. Accountants, Financial, 1966; 1 folder (Box 618, Folder 15)
    - Tax Exemption Status, Financial, 1966; 1 folder (Box 618, Folder 16)
    - Termination of Apfel and Englander as ACLU Accountants, Financial, 1966; 1 folder (Box 618, Folder 17)
    - Book Proposal, 1967; 1 folder (Box 618, Folder 18)
    - Life Magazine, 1967; 1 folder (Box 618, Folder 19)
    - Markmann, C, 1967; 1 folder (Box 618, Folder 20)
    - New York Library Archive, 1967; 1 folder (Box 618, Folder 21)
    - New York Times, 1967; 1 folder (Box 618, Folder 22)
    - Office Memos, 1967; 1 folder (Box 618, Folder 23)
    - National Arts and Communications Division, 1967; 1 folder (Box 619, Folder 1)
    - Organizational Matters, 1967; 1 folder (Box 619, Folder 2)
    - Outside Publishers, 1967; 1 folder (Box 619, Folder 3)
    - Princeton University Archives, 1967; 1 folder (Box 619, Folder 4)
    - Proposed ACLU Educational Program, 1967; 1 folder (Box 619, Folder 5)
    - Requests for Quotes and Reprints, 1967; 1 folder (Box 619, Folder 6)
    - Requests for Speakers, 1967; 1 folder (Box 619, Folder 7)
    - "The Unamerican", 1967; 1 folder (Box 619, Folder 8)
    - Grant in Memory of Clement Wells, Financial, 1967; 1 folder (Box 619, Folder 9)
    - Funds, Grants, bequests, Financial, 1967; 1 folder (Box 619, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, Requests for Information and Assistance, 1967; 1 folder (Box 619, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 1967; 1 folder (Box 619, Folder 12)
    - ACLU Book Service, 1968; 1 folder (Box 619, Folder 13)
    - ACLU Constitutional Revisions, 1968; 1 folder (Box 619, Folder 14)
    - ACLU Library, 1968; 1 folder (Box 619, Folder 15)
    - Bill of Rights Day, 1968; 1 folder (Box 619, Folder 16)
    - Board Correspondence, 1968; 1 folder (Box 619, Folder 17)
    - "Burden of Blame", 1968; 1 folder (Box 619, Folder 18)
    - "Civil Liberties", 1966; 1968; 1 folder (Box 619, Folder 19)
    - Education Workshop - Survey-Action Section", 1968; 1 folder (Box 619, Folder 20)
    - Frankel, Osmond 80th Birthday, 1968; 1 folder (Box 619, Folder 21)
    - Haskell, G.: "Structure, function and mythology", 1968; 1 folder (Box 619, Folder 22)
    - Office Memos, 1968; 1 folder (Box 619, Folder 23)
    - Organizations of National Staff, 1968; 1 folder (Box 620, Folder 1)
    - Outside Publishers, 1968; 1 folder (Box 620, Folder 2)
    - Princeton University Archives, 1968; 1 folder (Box 620, Folder 3)
    - Proposed Ombudsman Law, 1968; 1 folder (Box 620, Folder 4)
    - Requests for Speakers, 1968; 1 folder (Box 620, Folder 5)
    - Study on ACLU Activities by E. Levitt, 1968; 1 folder (Box 620, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, Deaths, 1968; 1 folder (Box 620, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, Financial, 1968; 1 folder (Box 620, Folder 8)
    - Budget, Audit, Investment Miscellaneous, Financial, 1968; 2 folders (Box 620, Folder 9-10)
    - Funds and Grants, Financial, 1968; 1 folder (Box 620, Folder 11)
    - Pension Plan, Financial, 1968; 1 folder (Box 620, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous, Requests for Information, 1968; 1 folder (Box 620, Folder 13)
    - Reprints, Requests for Information, 1968; 1 folder (Box 620, Folder 14)
    - Tapes and Films, Requests for Information, 1968; 1 folder (Box 620, Folder 15)
    - American-Arab Relations, 1969; 1 folder (Box 620, Folder 16)
    - ACLU Library, 1969; 1 folder (Box 620, Folder 17)
    - Bill of Rights Day, 1969; 1 folder (Box 621, Folder 1)
    - "Civil Liberties" Revisions, 1969; 1 folder (Box 621, Folder 2)
    - "Civil Liberties and the Diverse Society", 1969; 1 folder (Box 621, Folder 3)
    - Computer Contract with Apparel Industries Data Service, 1969; 1 folder (Box 621, Folder 4)
    - Drafts and Working papers, 1969; 1 folder (Box 621, Folder 5)
    - Litigation Guide, 1969; 1 folder (Box 621, Folder 6)
    - New York Times, 1969; 1 folder (Box 621, Folder 7)
    - Office Administration, 1969; 1 folder (Box 621, Folder 8)
    - Office Memos, 1969; 1 folder (Box 621, Folder 9)
    - Organizational Matters, 1969; 1 folder (Box 621, Folder 10)
    - Outside Publishers, 1969; 1 folder (Box 621, Folder 11)
    - Possible Relocation of Headquarters, 1969; 1 folder (Box 621, Folder 12)
    - Princeton University Archives, 1969; 1 folder (Box 621, Folder 13)
    - Reinstatement of Elizabeth Gurley Flynn, 1969; 1 folder (Box 621, Folder 14)
    - Request for Homosexual Campaign, 1969; 1 folder (Box 621, Folder 15)
    - Requests for Speakers, 1969; 1 folder (Box 621, Folder 16)
    - Subscriptions List, 1969; 1 folder (Box 621, Folder 17)
    - Testimonial Dinner for Ernest Angell's 80th Birthday and Retirement, 1969; 2 folders (Box 621, Folder 18-19)
    - Controller's Department, Financial, 1969; 1 folder (Box 621, Folder 21)
    - Funds, Grants and Bequests, Financial, 1969; 1 folder (Box 621, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous, Requests for Information, 1969; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 1)
    - Reprints, Requests for Information, 1969; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 2)
    - Tapes and Films, Requests for Information, 1969; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reports, Miscellaneous, 1970; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 4)
    - Blood, Sweat and Tears Concert, Miscellaneous, 1970; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 5)
    - Civil Liberties Course Outline, Miscellaneous, 1970; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 6)
    - Data Processing System, Miscellaneous, 1970; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 7)
    - Princeton University Archives, Miscellaneous, 1970; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 8)
    - Funds, Grants and Bequests, Financial, 1970; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 9)
    - Retirement Plan, Financial, 1970; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 10)
    - Wakefield, E.I., Deaths, 1970; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 11)
    - Funds, Grants and Bequests, 1971; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 12)
    - Princeton University Archives, 1971; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 13)
    - Constitution of ACLU, 1972; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 14)
    - 200th Anniversary of the American Revolution, 1972; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 15)
    - Activity Report, 1976; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 16)
    - Baldwin's Review of Peggy Lamson's Book, 1976; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 17)
    - Prison Construction, 1976; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 18)
    - Academic Division Proposal, 1977; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 19)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1977; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 20)
    - Pension Plan, Financial, 1977; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 21)
    - Mandatory Seat Belts, Requests for Information, 1977; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 22)
    - Location of National Office, 1978; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 23)
    - Management Survey, 1978; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 23a)
    - Communications Proposal, 1985; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 24)
    - Bork, Robert, 1987; 1 folder (Box 622, Folder 25)